cyberoam.com 2018-10-11

# Cyberoam Privacy Policy – Cyberoam

This document was last updated on 13th December 2015.

**General**  
This is the privacy policy of **Sophos Technologies Private Limited** (Formerly known as “Cyberoam Technologies Private Limited”.) Hereinafter referred to as “ **Cyberoam** ” for sake of convenience. 

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of your personal data. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we collect and use your personal data, for example when you contact us, visit one of our websites (each a “Site”), apply for a job, or use our products and services. 

Whenever you give us personal data, you are consenting to its collection and use in accordance with this privacy policy. 

**What personal data do we collect?**  
We may collect personal data such as your name, company position, address, telephone number, mobile number, fax number, email address, credit card details, age, IP address, and account usernames. 

**How do you use my personal data?**  
If you provide personal data to us, we will collect that information and use it for the purposes for which you have provided it and in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Browsing our Site**  
Every time you connect to the Site, we store a log of your visit that shows the unique number your machine uses when it is connected to the Internet – its IP address. This tells us what your machine has looked at, whether the page request was successful or not and which browser your machine used to view the pages. This data is used for statistical purposes as well as to help customize the user experience as you browse the Site. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of text that gets entered into the memory of your browser by a website, allowing the website to store information on your machine and later retrieve it. Some of our pages use cookies so that we can distinguish you from other users and better serve you when you return to the Site. Cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the onsite experience. Most internet browsers allow the use of cookies to be enabled or disabled. To find out more about cookies and how to disable them, please refer to [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). For specific instructions about how to enable or disable cookies on your computer, please also refer to the documentation for your browser software. If you do not wish to allow cookies, please disable cookies before continuing to use this website. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the website may be functionally limited.

**Job applicants**  
If you are making a job application or inquiry, you may provide us with a copy of your CV or other relevant information. We may use this information for the purpose of considering your application or inquiry. Except when you explicitly request otherwise, we may keep this information on file for future reference.

**Partner portal**  
Our resellers and distributors may visit our partner portal Site. We may use the customer and prospect information provided on that Site in order to provide the products and services.

**Providing products and services**  
If you purchase or use our products or services, we may use your personal data for purposes which include but are not limited to:

  * verifying your credentials, 
  * carrying out end user compliance checks for export control purposes, 
  * issuing virus information alerts and other alert messages, 
  * providing training sessions for which you have registered, 
  * providing maintenance and technical support, 
  * providing information about product upgrades, updates and renewals, 
  * generating logs, statistics and reports on service usage, service performance and malware infection, 
  * developing and enhancing products, services, and our infrastructure, 
  * processing orders and generating billing information.

Certain products and services may include features that collect additional personal data for other purposes, as described below. For detailed information, please also refer to the applicable product or service description.

**Market research**  
If you participate in surveys, we may use your personal data to carry out market research. This research is conducted for our internal business and training purposes and will improve our understanding of our users’ demographics, interests and behaviour. This research is usually compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis.

**Marketing and promotions**  
We (or our group companies, resellers and other selected third parties acting on our behalf) may contact you from time to time in order to provide you with information about products and services that may be of interest to you. You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes, but if you do so, we may need to share your contact information with third parties for the limited purpose of ensuring that you do not receive marketing communications from them on our behalf.

**Email communications**  
Emails offering software downloads or free product trials of our products will usually link to web pages on www.cyberoam.com, customer.cyberoam.com, download.cyberoam.com, csc.cyberoam.com, kb.cyberoam.com, play.google.com, itunes.apple.com, <http://sourceforge.net/projects/cyberoam-iview/>,[www.sophos.com](http://www.sophos.com/), or www.web.sophos.com. If you receive an email which claims to come from us but does not use these domains, or if you are suspicious that an email may not be approved by us, then please send a copy of the email to us at [support@cyberoam.com](mailto:support@cyberoam.com) so we can investigate.

We have published best practice guidelines to help internet users learn how to avoid phishing emails at [http:phishing.html](http://phishing.html/).

**With whom might we share your personal data?**  
We have international sites and users all over the world. When you give us personal data, that data may be used, processed or stored anywhere in the world by any of our group companies. 

We may also pass your personal data to suppliers, service providers, subcontractors, agents, distributors, resellers and other partners worldwide, in order to provide you with the information, products and services that you requested or otherwise for the purposes described in this privacy policy.

In the event that we receive requests from government departments, agencies or other official bodies, we will only disclose your information if and to the extent that we believe we are legally required to do so (for example upon receipt of a court order, warrant, subpoena or equivalent).

Except as set out above, we will not disclose your personal data save where we need to do so in order to enforce our rights.  
Whenever we share personal data, we take all reasonable steps to ensure that it is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Links**  
This privacy policy applies to personal data collected by us. If an email or Site contains links to a third party site, please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site, and to read the privacy policy of other sites that collect personal data. 

**Security**  
We endeavour to hold all personal data securely in accordance with our internal security procedures and applicable law.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any other network can be guaranteed as 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal data, we cannot ensure and do not warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and this information is transmitted at your own risk.

If you have been given log-in details to provide you with access to certain parts of our Site (for example our partner portal), you are responsible for keeping those details confidential.

**Contact**  
If you want to request any information about your personal data or believe that we are holding incorrect personal data on you, please contact [support@cyberoam.com](mailto:support@cyberoam.com). It is possible to obtain a copy of the information that we hold on you. A nominal charge may be made to cover administrative costs involved.

**Notification of changes**  
This privacy policy was last updated on 13th December 2015. We reserve the right to amend or vary this policy at any time and the revised policy will apply from the date posted on the Site. You accept that by doing this, we have provided you with sufficient notice of the amendment or variation.

Copyright © 1999 – 2015  
Sophos Technologies Private Limited. All Rights reserved.
